Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.fourtee Mss.B.B61.inventory14
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents W
  - Wilson, Louis N. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 5; 1p
    - From M. A> McDonald, 1891 Aug. 18
    - To Boas, 1893 Mar. 18; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 21; 1p
  - Wilson, N. Lane (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 4
  - Wilson, R. H. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1913 May 20
  - Wilson, Rufus R. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 16; 1p
  - Wilson, Thomas (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1896 Dec. 28
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 12
  - Wilson, Walter (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1931 July 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 12; 1p
  - Wilson, W. B. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1919 July 31; 1p
    - See Boas to Smedley, A., 1919 July 31
  - Wilson, Woodrow (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 5
    - Wilson, Woodrow (from Hervey, W. A.), 1917 Nov. 27
  - Winchell, Walter (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 19; 1p
    - Enc. with Boas, F. (to Fraenkel, O.), 1940 Apr. 19
  - Winckel, F. von (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 1; 4p
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 20; 3p
  - Wind, Edgar (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 19; 2p
  - Windmüller, Louis (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 25
  - Winekelmann, E. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 31
  - Winkhovitch, Mary K. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 13; 2p
  - Winkler, Max (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 10; 1p
  - Winkow (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 23
  - Winlock, Herbert E. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 29; 1p
  - Winnikow, T. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1930 May 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 7; 1p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1930, 3p
  - Winser, Beatrice (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 30; 1p
  - Winser, John H. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1900 Oct. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 22
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1894 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1904 Apr. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 Oct. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Oct. 24; 1p
  - Winslow, C. E. A. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 28; 1p
  - Winter, Carl (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1908 May 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 31
  - Winter, Miss Ella (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1933 May 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 28; 1p
  - Winter, Dr. Ernst Karl (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 5; 1p
  - Winter, Joseph (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 May 1; 1p
  - Winterfeld, von (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 28; 1p
  - Winterrowd, W. H. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 4; 2p
  - Winthuis, Dr. J. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 28; 2p
  - Wintze, von. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 29
  - Wipplinger, Natalie (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 4; 2p
  - Wirbelauer, W. L. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1920 July 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 4; 1p
  - Wirth, Dr. Louis (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1931 Aug. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 3; 1p
  - Wis. Marine & Fire Ins. Co, Bank (Mitchell, J. L.) (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1886 Dec. 11; 1p
  - Wisbrun, A. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 22; 3p
  - Wisdom, Charles (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 18; 2p
      Enc: Outline of his paper
  - Wise, Jonah B. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1936 Sep. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 14; 1p
  - Wise, Raymond (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1926 June 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 July 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 July 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 4; 1p
  - Wise, Stephen S. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1938 June 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 22; 1p
      Enc: Statement by American educators on the 24th anniveraary of the Balfour Declaration.
  - Wiskott, C. T. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1894 Feb. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1894 Mar. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1894 May 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1894 May 11; 1p
  - Wissenschaftliche Gesellschaft Director (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 1; 1p
  - Wissler, Clark (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1903 May 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 June 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 June 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 Aug. 2
    - From Boas, 1905 Aug. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 15
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 19
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 19
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 11
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 12
    - From Boas, 1915 May 22
    - See Boas, F. (to Gordon, G. B.), 1916 May 22
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 25
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 8
    - See Boas, F. (to Dixon, R. B.), 1916 Dec. 8
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Amer. Anthropological Ass, Publication Committee, 1920 Nov. 5; 3p
    - From Jochelson, W., 1927 May 18
    - From Laufer, B., 1920 Nov. 13; 3p
    - To Members of the Committee on Policy Amer, Anthropological Ass., 1921 Nov. 15; 5p
    - To Michelson, T.
    - See Michelson, 1924 Feb. 25
    - To Moorehead, W. K., 1935 Oct. 10; 1p
    - Enc. with Moorehead, W. K., 1935 Oct. 15
    - From Rau, C., 1926 Aug. 30
    - To Sapir, E., 1926 Aug.; 1p
    - Note written on Rau, C., 1926 Aug. 30
    - To Seligman, E. R., 1926 Mar. 17; 1p
    - Enc. with Seligman, E. R., 1926 Mar. 31
  - Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology (Box 97)
    See Donaldson, Henry H.
    See Greeman, W. J.
    See Lawton, G. L.
  - Witherspoon, Miss Frances (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 17; 1p
  - Witmer, Lightner (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1907 May 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 May 16; 1p
  - Witt, Bert (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 10; 1p
  - Witt, G. (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1930 June 4; 1p
  - Wittenby, Gertrude (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 22; 1p
      See Gestures
    - See Wittenby, Gertrude, 1935 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 29; 1p
  - Wittfogel, Esther Schiff (Goldfrank) (Box 97)
    See Goldfrank, Esther Schiff
  - Wittfogel, Karl August (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1938 May 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 29; 1p
  - Wittrock, G. L. (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1931 July 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 8; 1p
  - Witty, Paul A. (Box 97)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on cultures and democracy in Spain. Replies., 1938 Jan.
  - Woerishoffer, Anna (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 18; 1p
  - Wohlauer (Box 97)
    - From Kaufmann, M., 1926 Mar. 25
  - Wohlauer, Erich (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 12; 2p
  - Wohlauer, J. (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 13; 1p
  - Wohlauer, Minnie (Box 97)
    - See Wohlauer, Erich Margin, 1939 July 12
  - Wolcott, C. P. (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 22; 1p
  - Wolf, Bertha (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 10; 3p
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 21; 4p
  - Wolf, Gerhard (Gerd - J. G.) (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 24; 3p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 June 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 June 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Dec. 6; 3p
    - From Boas, 1919 Feb. 21; 3p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 May 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 May 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 June 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Dec. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 10; 3p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 15; 4p
  - Wolf, Gustav (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 30; 1p
    - Enc: Vita and publications, 1938 Nov. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 11; 1p
  - Wolf, I. S. (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 13; 3p
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 June 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 July 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 4; 1p
  - Wolf, J. S. (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 10; 2p
  - Wolf, Laurence G. (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1942 Oct. 22; 1p
  - Wolf, Max (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 31; 1p
  - Wolf, Theodore (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 22; 1p
  - Wolfe, H. K. (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1891 Sep. 26
  - Wolff, Ernst V. (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 21; 1p
  - Wolff, Gertrude Miss (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 25; 1p
  - Wolff, Herbert (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 30; 1p
  - Wolfson, Harry A. (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1935 June 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 June 26; 1p
  - Wolfson, Mildred H. (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 11; 1p
  - Wolfson, Theresa (Box 97)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., 1938 Jan.
  - Wolkwitz, E. (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 13; 1p
  - Woll, F. A. (Frederick) (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 14; 1p
  - Wolman, Leo (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 11; 1p
    - See Pegram, G. B. (to Cabanellas), 1937 Feb. 11
  - Wolters, Paul (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 18; 3p
  - Woner, Adolph (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 22; 1p
  - Wood (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 4
  - Wood, Austin B. (Box 97)
    - See Boas, F. (Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies.), 1938 Jan.
  - Wood, A. F. (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 20; 1p
  - Wood, Edith Elmer (Box 97)
    - To Hodge, F. W., 1903 Feb. 28; 3p
  - Wood, F. C. (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 30; 1p
  - Wood, Henry (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 2; 3p
    - From Urbach, Anna, 1923 Aug. 31; 1p
  - Wood, Lee B. (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 12; 1p
  - Wood, L. Hollingsworth (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 24; 1p
      Enc. Signed appeal
  - Wood, Morey A. (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 16; 1p
  - Wood, Wallace (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1893 July 22; 3p
  - Wood, Wilbur (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 31; 1p
      Enc: Newspaper clipping
  - Woodard, Fred B. (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1932 July 24; 1p
  - Woodberg (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 4
  - Woodbridge, Prof. Frederick J. E. (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 26
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 28
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 7
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 30
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 20
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Sep. 13
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 15; 6p
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 21; 5p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 20; 5p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 May 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 June 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 June 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 7; 4p
    - From Boas, 1919 Feb. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 3; 3p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 May 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 May 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 19; 3p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 21; 3p
    - From Boas, 1925 May 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 July 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 May 10; 1p
    - Enc: See Woodbridge, F. J. E. (to Butler, N.M.), 1918 May 10
    - To Boas, 1918 June 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 May 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 July 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Butler, N.M., 1918 May 10; 1p
    - Enc. originally with Woodbridge, F.J.E. (to Boas, F.), 1918 May 10
    - From Cattell, J. M., 1918 Nov. 25; 2p
  - Woodbury, Robert Morse (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 July 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aprl 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 25; 1p
      Enc: Table of statistics
    - To Boas, 1930 July 1; 1p
  - Woodley, Sam (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 29; 1p
  - Woodring, H. H. (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 29; 1p
  - Woods, Erville B. (Box 97)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., 1938 Jan.
  - Woodson, C. G. (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 June 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 May 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 May 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 May 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Sep. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 May 7
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Sep. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 29; 1p
    - Enc: Shepard, J. E. (to Woodson), 1926 May 28
    - To Boas, 1926 May 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 16; 1p
    - Enc: Memorandum from Locke, A.L. To Woodson, C. G., 1926 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Sep. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 18; 1p
    - From Locke, A. L.
    - Enc. with Woodson, C. G., 1926 Nov. 16
    - From Shepard, J. E., 1926 May 28
    - Enc. with Woodson, C. G., 1926 May 29
  - Woodward, Arthur (Box 97)
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 9; 1p
  - Woodward, Frederick (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 7; 1p
  - Woodward, J. L. (Julian) (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 19; 1p
  - Woodword, Miss Ellen S. (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 12; 1p
  - Woodward, Prof. R. S. -- also see Woodworth, R.S. (Box 97)
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 13
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 13
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1906 June 15
    - From Boas, 1906 Sep. 24
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1907 May 3
    - From Boas, 1907 May 22
    - From Boas, 1907 May 25
    - From Boas, 1907 May 27
    - From Boas, 1907 May 31
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 26; 7p
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 30
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1908 May 4
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 5; 5p
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 31
    - Found at end of Dec. 1909, 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1910 May 9
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 17; 3p
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 8
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1898 May 18
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1906 June 27
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 28
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 24
    - To Boas, 1907 May 6
    - To Boas, 1907 May 21
    - To Boas, 1907 May 23
    - To Boas, 1907 May 24
    - To Boas, 1907 May 27
    - To Boas, 1907 May 28
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 28
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1908 May 8
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1910 June 9
    - To Boas, 1911 Oct. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 4; 4p
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 24; 1p
    - From McGee, W. J., 1905 Mar. 20
    - To Peabody, G. F., 1907 May 9
  - Woodworth, R. S. -- also see Woodward, Prof. R. S. (Box 97-98)
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 12; 1p
    - Enc: Resolutions adopted by faculty of Philosophy., 1925 Feb. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 4
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 3; 1p
    - See National Research Council, 1925 Feb. 18
    - Africa-Negro 7p 1927, 1925 Feb. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 27; 1p